# Jessica Stapp

1509 27th Street #3 • Sacramento, CA 95816 (773) 241-0749 • STAPP9@GMAIL.COM

## **Summary**

I have worked in the customer service industry for over twelve years in a variety of highly-skilled jobs. I eagerly engage with clients, focusing on clear communication and personalizing their experience. I am a fast learner, a team-player, and can follow directions and instructions precisely. I handle criticism with a positive attitude. I am looking for a customer service position and can work in a team or independently.

# **Experience**

#### Asha Urban Baths, Sacramento, CA - Massage Therapist

**APRIL 14 - PRESENT** 

- Locate clients and customize their professional massage, paying attention to their specific needs..
- Maintain cleanliness and relaxing environment in massage room and within facilities.
- Keep track of supplies needed and work as a team with other therapists and coworkers.

#### **Piedmont Spa, Oakland, CA - Massage Therapist, Reception**

MAY 2018 - MARCH 2019

- Intake clients, customize professional massage for clients.
- Check clients in and out at desk, book appointments, answer calls and emails.
- Cleaning duties include laundry, sanitizing, refilling, stocking.

### Kriser's: Natural Pet, Chicago, IL - Dog Groomer, Sales Associate

APRIL 2009 - FEBRUARY 2018

- Speak with customers about their pets' needs and work with them to customize experience.
- Bathe, dry, trim dogs' hair with empathy and efficiency.
- Maintain relations with long-time regulars.
- Maintain cleanliness and functionality of grooming space and equipment, stocking.
- Book appointments and input schedules.

#### Education

Malcolm X City College, Chicago, IL - Advanced Massage Therapy JANUARY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

Intensive massage therapy program for certification.. Two internships: Wellfit Tri-athlete Training and Massage Envy. Student Government Treasurer. Sent to LEAD 365 in Florida with our SGA.

#### **University of Oregon, Eugene, OR** - Bachelor of Arts

**SEPTEMBER 2002 - MAY 2007** 

Art Major: Drawing, Painting, Sculpture, Printmaking (woodblock and lithography), Ceramics, Comics, and Photography.

#### Skills

Computer: Google Docs, Word, Google Sheets, MindBody, Editing, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, and APIs

Strong communication skills, Organization, Punctuality, Attention to detail, Quick learner.